<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amin&#39;s Den</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amin&#39;s Den</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing a Motion Blur Effect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/motionblur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 10:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/motionblur/</guid>
      <description>Photo: The Last of Us Part II  Recently, I explored different Motion Blur techniques being used in the video game industry. Now, I have decided to jot down the result of this research.
At the first glance, I found several per-pixel motion blur approaches, but they did not impress me. To explain why I was not satisfied with the results, some history lessons are required!
Screen-space Motion Blur My main issue with the trivial approaches was that they would only take the camera motion into account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 10:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Computers have always played a pivotal role in my life. We had one when I was only five, and I started to pick up on them at the age of ten. Back then, all I wanted was to play around with the display buffer in DOS to depict something on the screen. Therefore, after a while, I made my first game called Snake! Since then, I have become a self-thought machine, so that is why I&amp;rsquo;m quite comfortable with learning new concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mithra Graphics Renderer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mithra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mithra/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mithra&amp;rdquo; is a physically-based graphics renderer featuring many new and modern rendering techniques such as image-based lighting, shadow-mapping, etc. I have also proposed and defended this renderer as my B.Sc. project at Amirkabir University of Technology (Tehran Polytechnic).
 This is a showcase of some of its main features. Hopefully, in near future, I will share more about the development process in this blog.‍
   #slide-window { position: relative; width: 700px; height: 350px; overflow: hidden; top: 0px; left: 0px; } #slides-list { width: 700px; height: 350px; position: absolute; margin: 0px; padding: 0px; -webkit-transform: translate3d(0px, 0px, 0px); transform: translate3d(0px, 0px, 0px); transition: all 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My journey at Amirkabir Robotic Center (ARC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/arc/</guid>
      <description>While I was a researcher at Amirkabir University of Technology Robotic Center, I&amp;rsquo;ve developed a simulation environment using Unity3D game engine to connect to ROS framework. This tool was mostly used to test our AI, movement, localization, and vision systems.
 We needed this environment because other teams such as mechanic or electronic team would want to take robots to work on them and at the same time software team needed to continue their development plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archives/</guid>
      <description>archives</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Series</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/series/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/series/</guid>
      <description>series</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tags/</guid>
      <description>tags</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
